=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 18=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 18 =
Do me a favor.
أعمل لي معروفا.
No.
رقم.
I'm occupied now.
أنا مشغول الآن.
Miss.
يغيب.
He's got HIV.
إنه مصاب بفيروس نقص المناعة البشرية.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Why do I have a friend like you?
لماذا لدي صديق مثلك؟
What a nice friend.
يا له من صديق لطيف.
Do me a favor.
أعمل لي معروفا.
I promise to find you a hotter one.
أعدك أن أجد لك أكثر سخونة.
No.
رقم.
You're certainly here for Gu Chengze.
أنت بالتأكيد هنا من أجل Gu Chengze.
I thought you broke up.
اعتقدت أنك انفصلت.
Can't you let him alone?
لا يمكنك تركه وحده؟
I lied to him in the first place.
لقد كذبت عليه في المقام الأول.
By helping him this time
بمساعدته هذه المرة
we would be even.
سنكون حتى.
Owe nothing to each other.
مدينون بشيء لبعضنا البعض.
You're not meaning what your say.
أنت لا تعني ما تقوله.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
What's the favor?
ما هو صالح؟
Isn't it the famous
أليس من المشهور
superstar Jin Sula?
النجم جين سولا؟
What?
ماذا؟
Let me introduce myself.
دعني أقدم نفسي.
I am Eason from the V Group.
أنا إيسون من V Group.
I wonder if Miss Jin Sula is interested
أتساءل عما إذا كانت الآنسة جين سولا مهتمة
in joining V Group?
في الانضمام إلى V Group؟
I'll ponder it.
سوف أفكر فيه.
Good.
جيد.
When you make up your mind,
عندما تتخذ قرارك ،
bring your entry form and health report to me.
إحضار استمارة الدخول والتقرير الصحي لي.
I'll be waiting for you.
سوف اكون في انتظارك.
(CT Room)
(غرفة التصوير المقطعي المحوسب)
Please do some modification to my report,
الرجاء إجراء بعض التعديل على تقريري ،
and don't blow up my fake pregnancy plan.
ولا تفجر خطة الحمل المزيفة.
Miss,
يغيب،
keep it quiet.
يبقيه هادئا.
It's not that easy.
الأمر ليس بهذه السهولة.
I could get fired because of this.
يمكن أن أطرد بسبب هذا.
I might even go to jail.
حتى أنني قد أذهب إلى السجن.
You'll get paid.
سوف تدفع لك.
Do it quick.
افعلها بسرعة.
How about this.
وماذا عن هذا.
You take the test now,
تأخذ الاختبار الآن ،
and I'll figure a way out.
وسأجد طريقة للخروج.
Better not to blow it up.
من الأفضل عدم تفجيرها.
Dr. Zhang.
الدكتور تشانغ.
Dr. Jia wants to talk to you.
يريد الدكتور جيا التحدث معك.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Dr. Wang, why are you still here?
دكتور وانج ، لماذا مازلت هنا؟
I'm looking up one of the patients' case.
أنا أبحث عن حالة واحدة من المرضى.
How dare you modify patient's case?
كيف تجرؤ على تعديل حالة المريض؟
Don't you know that's illegal?
ألا تعلم أن هذا غير قانوني؟
Dr. Zhang.
الدكتور تشانغ.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
You're welcome. Thanks for notifying me.
على الرحب والسعة.  شكرا لإخطاري.
He could've gotten his own way.
كان يمكن أن يكون قد حصل على طريقه الخاص.
Here are documents that prove Jin Sula's fake pregnancy.
ها هي الوثائق التي تثبت الحمل المزيف لجين سولا.
The doctor involved has been arrested.
تم القبض على الطبيب المتورط.
We also found the paparazzo who worked with Jin Sula.
وجدنا أيضًا المصورون الذين عملوا مع جين سولا.
He has confessed that
لقد اعترف بذلك
the private photo scandal with me and Jin Sula
فضيحة الصورة الخاصة معي وجين سولا
were all maneuvered by Jin Sula.
تم المناورة كلها من قبل جين سولا.
The whole drama ends right now.
الدراما كلها تنتهي الآن.
I'm not expecting to hear any gossips about it.
لا أتوقع سماع أي شائعات حول هذا الموضوع.
I...
أنا...
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Ah?
آه؟
It's not that hard to say thanks.
ليس من الصعب أن أقول شكرا.
I...
أنا...
(Does it really matter)
(هل هو مهم حقا)
(whether she's Xia Qianxun?)
(سواء كانت شيا تشيان شون؟)
Here are documents that prove Jin Sula's fake pregnancy.
ها هي الوثائق التي تثبت الحمل المزيف لجين سولا.
Xia Qiange!
شيا تشيانج!
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
Why?
لماذا ا؟
No way.
مستحيل.
I can't let it end like this.
لا أستطيع تركها تنتهي هكذا.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.